{
    "kind": "Dropdown",
    "questions": [
        {
            "title": "Select the correct word ",
            "Nomenclatura": "WBP3M1L4a.json",
            "header": "",
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "Listen __ the music!",
                    "options": [
                        "in",
                        "down",
                        "up",
                        "to"
                    ],
                    "correct": 3,
                    "type": "dropdown"
                },
                {
                    "question": "Sit __ and eat your supper!",
                    "options": [
                        "down",
                        "for",
                        "back",
                        "out"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0,
                    "type": "dropdown"
                },
                {
                    "question": "Hurry __ ! We're late!",
                    "options": [
                        "to",
                        "out",
                        "down",
                        "up"
                    ],
                    "correct": 3,
                    "type": "dropdown"
                },
                {
                    "question": "Look __ the letters.",
                    "options": [
                        "back",
                        "for",
                        "at",
                        "out"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2,
                    "type": "dropdown"
                },
                {
                    "question": "I'm looking __ my school bag, but I can't find it!",
                    "options": [
                        "down",
                        "for",
                        "back",
                        "out"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1,
                    "type": "dropdown"
                },
                {
                    "question": "Come __ ! Nice to see you!",
                    "options": [
                        "in",
                        "down",
                        "up",
                        "to"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0,
                    "type": "dropdown"
                },
                {
                    "question": "Come __ , Spot!",
                    "options": [
                        "down",
                        "back",
                        "to",
                        "in"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1,
                    "type": "dropdown"
                },
                {
                    "question": "I'm going __ ! See you later!",
                    "options": [
                        "down",
                        "for",
                        "back",
                        "out"
                    ],
                    "correct": 3,
                    "type": "dropdown"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "title": "Follow the lines. What do they do? What don't they do? Select True or False.",
            "Nomenclatura": "WBP3M2L7a.json",
            "header": "PP 20 ",
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "Mary plays the violin.",
                    "options": [
                        "TRUE",
                        "FALSE",
                        "",
                        ""
                    ],
                    "correct": 0,
                    "type": "dropdown"
                },
                {
                    "question": "She doesn't roller skate.",
                    "options": [
                        "TRUE",
                        "FALSE",
                        "",
                        ""
                    ],
                    "correct": 0,
                    "type": "dropdown"
                },
                {
                    "question": "Lety and Beatriz dance ballet. ",
                    "options": [
                        "TRUE",
                        "FALSE",
                        "",
                        ""
                    ],
                    "correct": 1,
                    "type": "dropdown"
                },
                {
                    "question": "They don't water sky.",
                    "options": [
                        "TRUE",
                        "FALSE",
                        "",
                        ""
                    ],
                    "correct": 1,
                    "type": "dropdown"
                },
                {
                    "question": "Roberto plays soccer.",
                    "options": [
                        "TRUE",
                        "FALSE",
                        "",
                        ""
                    ],
                    "correct": 1,
                    "type": "dropdown"
                },
                {
                    "question": "He swims. ",
                    "options": [
                        "TRUE",
                        "FALSE",
                        "",
                        ""
                    ],
                    "correct": 0,
                    "type": "dropdown"
                },
                {
                    "question": "Eduardo and Joel don't ski.",
                    "options": [
                        "TRUE",
                        "FALSE",
                        "",
                        ""
                    ],
                    "correct": 0,
                    "type": "dropdown"
                },
                {
                    "question": "They play basketball.",
                    "options": [
                        "TRUE",
                        "FALSE",
                        "",
                        ""
                    ],
                    "correct": 0,
                    "type": "dropdown"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "title": "Choose the correct answer.",
            "Nomenclatura": "WBP3M2L7a.json",
            "header": "",
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "Her favorite sport is skating, so she goes skating every week. ",
                    "options": [
                        "She often goes skating",
                        "She never goes skating",
                        "She sometimes goes skating.",
                        ""
                    ],
                    "correct": 0,
                    "type": "dropdown"
                },
                {
                    "question": "He watches cartoons just on friday afternoons. not every day.",
                    "options": [
                        "He never watches cartoons.",
                        "He sometimes watches cartoons.",
                        "He always watches cartoons.",
                        ""
                    ],
                    "correct": 1,
                    "type": "dropdown"
                },
                {
                    "question": "I read a book at bedtime every night.",
                    "options": [
                        "I often read a book at bedtime",
                        "I sometimes read a book at bedtime",
                        "I always read a book at bedtime.",
                        ""
                    ],
                    "correct": 2,
                    "type": "dropdown"
                },
                {
                    "question": "Her cousins live in a different country so she dosn't see them.",
                    "options": [
                        "She sometimes plays with her cousins.",
                        "She never plays with her cousins",
                        "She often plays with her cousins",
                        ""
                    ],
                    "correct": 1,
                    "type": "dropdown"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "title": "Complete the story and then read it aloud. ",
            "Nomenclatura": "WBP3M3L12a.json",
            "header": "",
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "Emma Early is never late! School starts __ 8:30,",
                    "options": [
                        "",
                        "",
                        "",
                        ""
                    ],
                    "correct": "at",
                    "type": "text"
                },
                {
                    "question": "so she always arrives __ 8:15.",
                    "options": [
                        "",
                        "",
                        "",
                        ""
                    ],
                    "correct": "at",
                    "type": "text"
                },
                {
                    "question": "__ Tuesday afternoons",
                    "options": [
                        "",
                        "",
                        "",
                        ""
                    ],
                    "correct": "On",
                    "type": "text"
                },
                {
                    "question": "her Karate class starts __ 4:00,",
                    "options": [
                        "",
                        "",
                        "",
                        ""
                    ],
                    "correct": "at",
                    "type": "text"
                },
                {
                    "question": "so she arrives at the gym __ 3:45.",
                    "options": [
                        "",
                        "",
                        "",
                        ""
                    ],
                    "correct": "at",
                    "type": "text"
                },
                {
                    "question": "__ Saturdays",
                    "options": [
                        "",
                        "",
                        "",
                        ""
                    ],
                    "correct": "On",
                    "type": "text"
                },
                {
                    "question": "__ the morning she has swimming class. She's always 15 minutes early.",
                    "options": [
                        "",
                        "",
                        "",
                        ""
                    ],
                    "correct": "in",
                    "type": "text"
                },
                {
                    "question": "She's the first person __ the swimming pool. ",
                    "options": [
                        "",
                        "",
                        "",
                        ""
                    ],
                    "correct": "at",
                    "type": "text"
                },
                {
                    "question": "__ the evenings she watches her favorite TV program.",
                    "options": [
                        "",
                        "",
                        "",
                        ""
                    ],
                    "correct": "In",
                    "type": "text"
                },
                {
                    "question": "It starts __ 7:00,",
                    "options": [
                        "",
                        "",
                        "",
                        ""
                    ],
                    "correct": "at",
                    "type": "text"
                },
                {
                    "question": "so Emma turns the TV on __ 6:45.",
                    "options": [
                        "",
                        "",
                        "",
                        ""
                    ],
                    "correct": "at",
                    "type": "text"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "title": "Complete the dictionary entries. ",
            "Nomenclatura": "WBP3M2L14b.json",
            "header": "",
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "__ / noun / a place where children go to learn.",
                    "options": [
                        "",
                        "",
                        "",
                        ""
                    ],
                    "correct": "school",
                    "type": "text"
                },
                {
                    "question": "__ / noun/ a building where you can see many valuable and important objects.",
                    "options": [
                        "",
                        "",
                        "",
                        ""
                    ],
                    "correct": "museum",
                    "type": "text"
                },
                {
                    "question": "__ /noun / a place you go to see movies.",
                    "options": [
                        "",
                        "",
                        "",
                        ""
                    ],
                    "correct": "movie theatre",
                    "type": "text"
                },
                {
                    "question": "__ / noun / in a town, an open area with grass and trees and places for children to play. ",
                    "options": [
                        "",
                        "",
                        "",
                        ""
                    ],
                    "correct": "park",
                    "type": "text"
                },
                {
                    "question": "__ / noun / a place where people buy gasoline for their cars.",
                    "options": [
                        "",
                        "",
                        "",
                        ""
                    ],
                    "correct": "gas station",
                    "type": "text"
                },
                {
                    "question": "__ / noun / a place where people can keep their money.",
                    "options": [
                        "",
                        "",
                        "",
                        ""
                    ],
                    "correct": "bank",
                    "type": "text"
                },
                {
                    "question": "__ / noun / a store where you buy toys.",
                    "options": [
                        "",
                        "",
                        "",
                        ""
                    ],
                    "correct": "toy store",
                    "type": "text"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "title": "Complete the sentences with the full date. ",
            "Nomenclatura": "WBP5M2L22a.json",
            "header": "",
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "New Year's Day is on __ (Jan 1st)",
                    "options": [
                        "",
                        "",
                        "",
                        ""
                    ],
                    "correct": "January first.",
                    "type": "text"
                },
                {
                    "question": "The Battle of Puebla is on __ (May 5th)",
                    "options": [
                        "",
                        "",
                        "",
                        ""
                    ],
                    "correct": "May fifth.",
                    "type": "text"
                },
                {
                    "question": "Mexican Independence Day is on __ (Sep 16th)",
                    "options": [
                        "",
                        "",
                        "",
                        ""
                    ],
                    "correct": "September sixteenth.",
                    "type": "text"
                },
                {
                    "question": "Day of the Virgin of Guadalupe is on __ (Dec 12th)",
                    "options": [
                        "",
                        "",
                        "",
                        ""
                    ],
                    "correct": "December twelfth.",
                    "type": "text"
                },
                {
                    "question": "Father's Day is  __ (June)",
                    "options": [
                        "",
                        "",
                        "",
                        ""
                    ],
                    "correct": "in June.",
                    "type": "text"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "title": "Write the months in order. ",
            "Nomenclatura": "WBP5M2L22b.json",
            "header": "",
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "1 __ ",
                    "options": [
                        "",
                        "",
                        "",
                        ""
                    ],
                    "correct": "January",
                    "type": "text"
                },
                {
                    "question": "2 __ ",
                    "options": [
                        "",
                        "",
                        "",
                        ""
                    ],
                    "correct": "February",
                    "type": "text"
                },
                {
                    "question": "3 __ ",
                    "options": [
                        "",
                        "",
                        "",
                        ""
                    ],
                    "correct": "March",
                    "type": "text"
                },
                {
                    "question": "4 __ ",
                    "options": [
                        "",
                        "",
                        "",
                        ""
                    ],
                    "correct": "April",
                    "type": "text"
                },
                {
                    "question": "5 __ ",
                    "options": [
                        "",
                        "",
                        "",
                        ""
                    ],
                    "correct": "May",
                    "type": "text"
                },
                {
                    "question": "6 __ ",
                    "options": [
                        "",
                        "",
                        "",
                        ""
                    ],
                    "correct": "June",
                    "type": "text"
                },
                {
                    "question": "7 __ ",
                    "options": [
                        "",
                        "",
                        "",
                        ""
                    ],
                    "correct": "July",
                    "type": "text"
                },
                {
                    "question": "8 __ ",
                    "options": [
                        "",
                        "",
                        "",
                        ""
                    ],
                    "correct": "August",
                    "type": "text"
                },
                {
                    "question": "9 __ ",
                    "options": [
                        "",
                        "",
                        "",
                        ""
                    ],
                    "correct": "September",
                    "type": "text"
                },
                {
                    "question": "10 __ ",
                    "options": [
                        "",
                        "",
                        "",
                        ""
                    ],
                    "correct": "October",
                    "type": "text"
                },
                {
                    "question": "11 __ ",
                    "options": [
                        "",
                        "",
                        "",
                        ""
                    ],
                    "correct": "November",
                    "type": "text"
                },
                {
                    "question": "12 __ ",
                    "options": [
                        "",
                        "",
                        "",
                        ""
                    ],
                    "correct": "December",
                    "type": "text"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "title": "Write the words.",
            "Nomenclatura": "WBP5M2L22b.json",
            "header": "",
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "1st",
                    "options": [
                        "",
                        "",
                        "",
                        ""
                    ],
                    "correct": "First",
                    "type": "text"
                },
                {
                    "question": "2nd",
                    "options": [
                        "",
                        "",
                        "",
                        ""
                    ],
                    "correct": "Second",
                    "type": "text"
                },
                {
                    "question": "3rd",
                    "options": [
                        "",
                        "",
                        "",
                        ""
                    ],
                    "correct": "Third",
                    "type": "text"
                },
                {
                    "question": "4th",
                    "options": [
                        "",
                        "",
                        "",
                        ""
                    ],
                    "correct": "Fourth",
                    "type": "text"
                },
                {
                    "question": "5th",
                    "options": [
                        "",
                        "",
                        "",
                        ""
                    ],
                    "correct": "Fifth",
                    "type": "text"
                },
                {
                    "question": "6th",
                    "options": [
                        "",
                        "",
                        "",
                        ""
                    ],
                    "correct": "Sixth",
                    "type": "text"
                },
                {
                    "question": "7th",
                    "options": [
                        "",
                        "",
                        "",
                        ""
                    ],
                    "correct": "Seventh",
                    "type": "text"
                },
                {
                    "question": "8th",
                    "options": [
                        "",
                        "",
                        "",
                        ""
                    ],
                    "correct": "Eight",
                    "type": "text"
                },
                {
                    "question": "9th",
                    "options": [
                        "",
                        "",
                        "",
                        ""
                    ],
                    "correct": "Ninth",
                    "type": "text"
                },
                {
                    "question": "10th",
                    "options": [
                        "",
                        "",
                        "",
                        ""
                    ],
                    "correct": "Tenth",
                    "type": "text"
                },
                {
                    "question": "11th",
                    "options": [
                        "",
                        "",
                        "",
                        ""
                    ],
                    "correct": "Eleventh",
                    "type": "text"
                },
                {
                    "question": "12th",
                    "options": [
                        "",
                        "",
                        "",
                        ""
                    ],
                    "correct": "Twelfth",
                    "type": "text"
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}